Audrey Beck Papers
© 2005 University of Connecticut
- Series VI: Women's Issues, 1950-1983
  - Women, 1979-1980 (Box 38:, Folder 1302)
    - Reports, 1972-1973 (Box 38:, Folder 1307)
    - Universities, 1972-1978 (Box 38:, Folder 1308)
    - University of Connecticut, 1972-1974 (Box 38:, Folder 1309)
    - Women, Infants and Children (WIC), 1975 (Box 38:, Folder 1310)
    - Women, Infants and Children (WIC), 1975-1976 (Box 38:, Folder 1311)
    - Women, Infants and Children (WIC), 1977-1978 (Box 38:, Folder 1312)
  - Women and education, 1971-1981 (Box 38:, Folder 1313)
  - Women and work, 1979-1982 (Box 38:, Folder 1314)
  - Women in politics, 1974-1980 (Box 38:, Folder 1315)
  - Women Today, 1981 (Box 38:, Folder 1316)
  - Women's Agenda, 1976 (Box 38:, Folder 1317)
  - Women's Bank, 1977-1978 (Box 38:, Folder 1318)
  - Women's Issues, 1974-1982 (Box 38:, Folder 1319)
  - Women's Legislative Review, 1973-1975 (Box 38:, Folder 1320)
  - Women's Political Caucus, 1971-1973 (Box 38:, Folder 1321)
  - Women's Political Caucus, 1974-1976 (Box 38:, Folder 1322)
- Series VII: District Matters, 1955-1981
  - Subseries A: Connecticut, 1972-1981
    - Bicentennial 29th District, 1976 (Box 38:, Folder 1323)
    - District Finance, 1977 (Box 38:, Folder 1324)
    - Eastern Connecticut, 1976-1981 (Box 38:, Folder 1325)
    - Eastern Connecticut Development Council, 1975-1977 (Box 38:, Folder 1326)
    - Eastern Connecticut Industry, 1975 (Box 38:, Folder 1327)
    - Eastern Connecticut Rural Reservation, 1972-1975 (Box 38:, Folder 1328)
    - Eastern CT Rural and Industrial Areas Preservation Committee, 1972-1977 (Box 38:, Folder 1329)
    - Eastern CT Rural and Industrial Areas Preservation Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 38:, Folder 1330)
    - Eastern Connecticut Towns, undated (Box 38:, Folder 1331)
    - Parent-Child Resources, 1974-1976 (Box 39:, Folder 1332-1334)
    - Youth Services Bureau, 1974-1977 (Box 39:, Folder 1335)
  - Subseries B: Mansfield, 1955-1980
    - Adamcik, undated (Box 39:, Folder 1336)
    - Bills—Richards, 1967 (Box 39:, Folder 1337)
    - Budget requests, 1968-1970 (Box 39:, Folder 1338)
    - Charter and local Government, 1970-1971 (Box 39:, Folder 1339)
    - Conservation Commission, 1969 (Box 39:, Folder 1340)
    - Correctional Center:Mansfield, 1969 (Box 39:, Folder 1341)
    - Eagleville Dam, undated (Box 39:, Folder 1342)
    - E.O. Smith, 1955-1977 (Box 39:, Folder 1343)
    - E.O. Smith, 1968-1974 (Box 39:, Folder 1344)
    - E.O. Smith, 1976 (Box 39:, Folder 1345)
    - Fay: Insurance Claim, 1969 (Box 39:, Folder 1346)
    - Gas and electric lines, 1969 (Box 39:, Folder 1347)
    - Hanks Hill Dam, 1964-1969 (Box 39:, Folder 1348)
    - Highway Bills, 1969 (Box 39:, Folder 1349)
    - Highway hearings, 1968-1970 (Box 39:, Folder 1350)
    - Highway maps and transparencies, undated (Box 39:, Folder 1351-1352)
    - Historical Society materials, 1969-1971 (Box 39:, Folder 1353)
    - Industrial Development Commission, 1968 (Box 39:, Folder 1354)
    - Liaison Committee, 1971 (Box 39:, Folder 1355)
    - Mansfield, 1969-1970 (Box 39:, Folder 1356)
    - Mansfield, 1970-1971 (Box 39:, Folder 1357)
    - Mansfield, 1975-1976 (Box 39:, Folder 1358)
    - Mansfield, 1976-1978 (Box 39:, Folder 1359)
      - Arrow Acres, 1975 (Box 40:, Folder 1360)
      - Day Care, 1969-1978 (Box 40:, Folder 1361)
      - Development, 1959-1965 (Box 40:, Folder 1362)
      - Democratic Council, 1969-1971 (Box 40:, Folder 1363)
      - Public Schools, 1968-1969 (Box 40:, Folder 1364)
      - Sewers, 1976 (Box 40:, Folder 1365)
      - Town Council, 1980 (Box 40:, Folder 1366)
      - Uniform Fiscal Year, undated (Box 40:, Folder 1367)
      - Voting Districts, 1980 (Box 40:, Folder 1368)
    - Mansfield Training Center, 1973 (Box 40:, Folder 1369)
    - Mansfield Training Center, 1974-1977 (Box 40:, Folder 1370)
    - Mansfield Training Center, 1976-1979 (Box 40:, Folder 1371)
    - Mountain Road Drainage problem, 1969 (Box 40:, Folder 1372)
    - Payments in Lieu of Taxes, Mansfield, 1968-1969 (Box 40:, Folder 1373)
    - Payments in Lieu of Taxes, Mansfield, 1969-1971 (Box 40:, Folder 1374)
    - Piontek Drainage: Rte. 195, 1969 (Box 40:, Folder 1375)
    - Prue, G. Tree Damage, 1974 (Box 40:, Folder 1376)
    - Report of Examination, 1968-1969 (Box 40:, Folder 1377)
    - Resolutions—Constituents, 1974-1976 (Box 40:, Folder 1378)
    - Resolutions—Whitney, Hannah, 1969, 1978 (Box 40:, Folder 1379)
    - Rte. 32 and Brown's Road, 1969-1973 (Box 40:, Folder 1380)
    - Rte. 195, 1972 (Box 40:, Folder 1381)
    - Rte. 275, 1967-1972 (Box 40:, Folder 1382)
    - Shopping Complex, Storrs, 1969-1971 (Box 40:, Folder 1383)
    - Stearns, W., 1970 (Box 40:, Folder 1384)
    - Tolland County Democratic Association, 1972 (Box 40:, Folder 1385)
    - Transportation: Audrey Beck, 1971-1973 (Box 40:, Folder 1386)
  - Subseries B: Organizations, 1972-1979
    - Aging—Triage, 1978 (Box 40:, Folder 1387)
    - Alcoholism, 1977 (Box 40:, Folder 1388)
    - Brooklyn Housing Authority, 1977-1979 (Box 40:, Folder 1389)
    - Correspondence, Committee of, 1975-1976 (Box 40:, Folder 1390)
    - Hear Town Grievances, Committee to, 1975-1977 (Box 40:, Folder 1391)
    - New England CT Regional Planning Agency, 1974-1978 (Box 40:, Folder 1392)
    - New England District Department of Health, 1974-1978 (Box 40:, Folder 1393)
    - Parish Hill Regional School, 1975 (Box 40:, Folder 1394)
    - Perception House, 1972-1977 (Box 40:, Folder 1395)
    - Private/Public Resource Expansion Project (P/PREP), 1976-1977 (Box 40:, Folder 1396)
    - Quebec Square, 1978 (Box 40:, Folder 1397)
    - Quinebaug Valley Community College, 1975-1976 (Box 40:, Folder 1398)
    - Quinebaug Valley Community College—Site selection, 1974-1979 (Box 40:, Folder 1399)
    - Quinebaug Valley Health and Welfare Council, 1974-1978 (Box 40:, Folder 1400)
    - Quinebaug Valley Senior Citizens Center, 1975-1978 (Box 41:, Folder 1401)
    - Railroads, 1974 (Box 41:, Folder 1402)
    - Railroads, 1975 (Box 41:, Folder 1403)
    - Railroads, 1976-1977 (Box 41:, Folder 1404)
    - Tolland County Extension Service, 1975-1977 (Box 41:, Folder 1405)
    - United Social and Mental Health Services, Inc., 1977 (Box 41:, Folder 1406)
    - UConn Alumni Association, 1972-1977 (Box 41:, Folder 1407)
    - UConn: Water Resource Institute, 1972-1977 (Box 41:, Folder 1407)
    - Windham Area Community Action Programs (WACAP), 1973-1975 (Box 41:, Folder 1409)
    - Windham Area Community Action Programs (WACAP), 1976-1977 (Box 41:, Folder 1410)
    - Windham Community Memorial Hospital, 1977 (Box 41:, Folder 1411)
    - Windham County Extension Center, 1973-1976 (Box 41:, Folder 1412)
    - Windham Regional Library, 1972-1975 (Box 41:, Folder 1413)
  - Subseries D: Towns, 1958-1981
    - Canterbury, 1974-1979 (Box 41:, Folder 1414)
    - Danielson, 1977-1980 (Box 41:, Folder 1415)
    - Killingly, 1972-1977 (Box 41:, Folder 1416)
    - Killingly: Schools, 1975-1977 (Box 41:, Folder 1417)
    - Plainfield, 1975-1978 (Box 41:, Folder 1418)
    - Plainfield: Chemicals in drums, 1978-1979 (Box 41:, Folder 1419)
    - Plainfield: Dog Track, 1976 (Box 41:, Folder 1420)
    - Putnam, 1975-1979 (Box 41:, Folder 1421)
    - Putnam: Day Kimball Hospital, 1975-1977 (Box 41:, Folder 1422)
    - Putnam: Economy, 1974-1975 (Box 41:, Folder 1423)
    - Scotland, 1975-1978 (Box 41:, Folder 1424)
    - Sterling: School Aid Bill and Environmental Protection, 1976-1979 (Box 41:, Folder 1425)
    - Thompson, 1975-1981 (Box 41:, Folder 1426)
    - Thompson: French River, 1974 (Box 42:, Folder 1427)
    - Thompson: French River, 1975 (Box 42:, Folder 1428)
    - Thompson: French River, 1976-1977 (Box 42:, Folder 1429)
    - Thompson: Industrial Park, 1977 (Box 42:, Folder 1430)
    - Thompson: Little League, 1972-1975 (Box 42:, Folder 1431)
    - Thompson: School Construction, 1976 (Box 42:, Folder 1432)
    - Thompson: Speedway, 1973-1975 (Box 42:, Folder 1433)
    - Voluntown, 1974-1978 (Box 42:, Folder 1434)
    - Willimantic, 1974-1975 (Box 42:, Folder 1435)
    - Willimantic, 1976-1980 (Box 42:, Folder 1436)
    - Willimantic: Armory, 1976-1978 (Box 42:, Folder 1437)
    - Willimantic: Library Service Center, 1973-1978 (Box 42:, Folder 1438)
    - Willimantic: Railroad, 1975-1979 (Box 42:, Folder 1439)
    - Windham, 1972-1980 (Box 42:, Folder 1440)
    - Windham Airport, 1969-1977 (Box 42:, Folder 1441)
    - Windham Hospital, 1970-1976 (Box 42:, Folder 1442)
    - Windham: Northeast-Windham Alcohol Council, 1974-1976 (Box 42:, Folder 1443-1444)
    - Windham Planning Region, 1960-1965 (Box 42:, Folder 1445)
    - Windham Planning Region, 1966-1967 (Box 42:, Folder 1446)
    - Windham Regional Mental Health Council, 1973-1977 (Box 42:, Folder 1447)
    - Windham Regional Planning Agency, 1968-1978 (Box 42:, Folder 1448)
    - Windham Regional Vocational Technical School, 1977-1978 (Box 42:, Folder 1449)
    - Man Power Charts, 1958-1962 (Box 42:, Folder 1450)
- Series VIII: Campaigns, Elections, and Democratic Party, undated, 1954-1982
  - Subseries A: Beck Campaigns and Democratic Party, undated, 1954-1982
    - Appointees, Democratic, 1975 (Box 43:, Folder 1451)
    - Beck early campaign coverage, 1973-1974 (Box 43:, Folder 1452)
    - Beck publications, 1974-1981 (Box 43:, Folder 1453)
    - Beck reports, 1974-1977 (Box 43:, Folder 1454)
    - Beck statements, undated (Box 43:, Folder 1455)
    - Campaign, 1968 (Box 43:, Folder 1456)
    - Campaign, 1972 (Box 43:, Folder 1457)
    - Campaign, 1972-1974 (Box 43:, Folder 1458)
    - Campaign, 1974 (Box 43:, Folder 1459)
    - Campaign, 1976 (Box 43:, Folder 1460)
    - Campaign, 1978-1980 (Box 43:, Folder 1461)
    - Campaign brochures, 1969-1978 (Box 43:, Folder 1462)
    - Campaign coverage, 1974 (Box 43:, Folder 1463)
    - Campaign coverage, 1974 (Box 43:, Folder 1464)
    - Campaign financing, 1973-1974 (Box 43:, Folder 1465)
    - Campaign funding, 1973 (Box 43:, Folder 1466)
    - Campaign issue material, 1973-1978 (Box 43:, Folder 1467)
    - Campaign Law—State, 1974 (Box 43:, Folder 1468)
    - Campaign newspaper clippings, 1976 (Box 43:, Folder 1469)
    - Connecticut CIO Council Voter Registration Survey, 1954 (Box 43:, Folder 1470)
    - Constituent Opinion Poll, undated (Box 43:, Folder 1471)
    - Contributors, 1972 (Box 43:, Folder 1472)
    - Contributors—Feminists, 1978 (Box 43:, Folder 1473)
    - Contributors mailing list, 1980 (Box 43:, Folder 1474)
    - Convention, 1976 (Box 43:, Folder 1475)
    - Delegates, 1978 (Box 43:, Folder 1476)
    - Delegate Lists, 1970 (Box 43:, Folder 1477)
    - Democratic Caucus, 1969-1973 (Box 43:, Folder 1478)
    - Democratic National Convention, 1972-1973 (Box 43:, Folder 1479)
    - Democratic Newsletter, 1969-1973 (Box 43:, Folder 1480)
    - Democratic Party, 1974-1976 (Box 43:, Folder 1481)
    - Democratic State Central Committee, 1971-1978 (Box 43:, Folder 1482)
    - Democratic Town Committees, 1978 (Box 43:, Folder 1483)
    - Democratic Women, 1977 (Box 43:, Folder 1484)
    - Democrats: State Newsletter, 1973 (Box 43:, Folder 1485)
    - Democrats: State Newsletter, 1973-1974 (Box 43:, Folder 1486)
    - District Mailing list, 1974-1976 (Box 43:, Folder 1487)
    - Duffey, J., 1969-1971 (Box 43:, Folder 1488)
    - Endorsements, 1972-1982 (Box 43:, Folder 1489)
    - Finances, 1976 (Box 43:, Folder 1490)
    - Fundraising, 1972-1974 (Box 43:, Folder 1491)
    - Grasso Re-election Committee, 1978 (Box 43:, Folder 1492)
    - National Democratic Party, 1974-1980 (Box 44:, Folder 1493)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1963-1973 (Box 44:, Folder 1494)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1974 (Box 44:, Folder 1495)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1975-1983 (Box 44:, Folder 1496)
    - Party Reform, 1969-1974 (Box 44:, Folder 1497)
    - Putnam Hearing, 1974 (Box 44:, Folder 1498)
    - Ratings—Beck, 1972-1976 (Box 44:, Folder 1499)
    - Secretary of State, 1978 (Box 44:, Folder 1500)
    - Senate Community Group - Speeches, 1974-1977 (Box 44:, Folder 1501)
    - Stolberg, Irving: Speaker of the House, 1982 (Box 44:, Folder 1502)
    - Tolland Newsletter, 1974 (Box 44:, Folder 1503)
    - Voting Record, 1973 (Box 44:, Folder 1504)
    - Voting Record, 1976 (Box 44:, Folder 1505)
    - Voting Record—Environment, 1971-1972 (Box 44:, Folder 1506)
  - Subseries B: Democratic State Platform, 1970-1982
    - Democratic Platform, 1974 (Box 44:, Folder 1507)
    - Democratic Platform Bills, 1972-1973 (Box 44:, Folder 1508)
    - Platform, 1970-1974 (Box 44:, Folder 1509)
    - Platform, 1974 (Box 44:, Folder 1510)
    - Platform, 1980-1982 (Box 44:, Folder 1511)
    - Platform Committee, 1970-1972 (Box 44:, Folder 1512)
    - Platform Committee Hearings, 1970 (Box 44:, Folder 1513)
    - Platform--WTIC Speeches, 1972-1976 (Box 44:, Folder 1514)
    - State Platform, 1972 (Box 44:, Folder 1515)
    - State Platform, 1976 (Box 44:, Folder 1516)
    - State Platform and Senate Speech, 1972-1976 (Box 44:, Folder 1517)
- Series IX: Publicity and Media Coverage, undated, 1962-1983
  - Appointment books and calendars, 1970-1972 (Box 44:, Folder 1518)
  - Appointment books and calendars, 1973-1975 (Box 44:, Folder 1519)
  - Appointment books and calendars, 1977-1978 (Box 44:, Folder 1520)
  - Appointment books and calendars, 1979-1980 (Box 44:, Folder 1521)
  - Appointment books and calendars, 1980-1983 (Box 44:, Folder 1522)
  - Beck in News, 1964-1970 (Box 45:, Folder 1523)
  - Beck in News, 1971-1973 (Box 45:, Folder 1524)
  - Beck in News, 1976-1983 (Box 45:, Folder 1525)
  - Commencement—Central Connecticut, 1977 (Box 45:, Folder 1526)
  - Crandall House—Governor's Visit, 1976 (Box 45:, Folder 1527)
  - Engagements, 1975-1976 (Box 45:, Folder 1528)
  - Engagements, 1977 (Box 45:, Folder 1529)
  - Hamilton Speech, 1976 (Box 45:, Folder 1530)
  - Invitations, 1976-1978 (Box 45:, Folder 1531)
  - League of Women Voters Speech, 1976 (Box 45:, Folder 1532)
  - Press releases, undated (Box 45:, Folder 1533)
  - Press releases, 1975 (Box 45:, Folder 1534)
  - Press releases, 1975-1979 (Box 45:, Folder 1535)
  - Publications referring to Beck, 1976 (Box 45:, Folder 1536)
  - Publicity, 1969-1973 (Box 45:, Folder 1537)
  - Publicity, 1974-1977 (Box 45:, Folder 1538)
  - Quinebaug Valley Community College—Governor's Visit, 1976 (Box 45:, Folder 1539)
  - Speeches, 1962-1970 (Box 45:, Folder 1540)
  - Speeches, 1971-1972 (Box 45:, Folder 1541)
  - Speeches, 1973-1975 (Box 45:, Folder 1542)
  - Speeches, 1976-1977 (Box 45:, Folder 1543)
  - Speeches, 1978-1983 (Box 45:, Folder 1544)
- Series X: Correspondence, 1955-1983
  - Arab boycott, 1977 (Box 45:, Folder 1545)
  - Augeo, Ben, 1976 (Box 45:, Folder 1546)
  - Bailey, J., 1968-1974 (Box 45:, Folder 1547)
  - Beck, Audrey P., 1970-1972 (Box 45:, Folder 1548)
  - Congratulations—official, 1968-1978 (Box 46:, Folder 1549)
  - Connecticut General Work, 1980 (Box 46:, Folder 1550)
  - Dempsey, J., 1969-1970 (Box 46:, Folder 1551)
  - Dodd, Chris, 1974-1975 (Box 46:, Folder 1552)
  - District, 1970-1976 (Box 46:, Folder 1553)
  - Driscoll, John, 1975 (Box 46:, Folder 1554)
  - Election Support (unofficial), 1974-1979 (Box 46:, Folder 1555)
  - Grasso, Ella, 1968-1976 (Box 46:, Folder 1556)
  - Hartford, 1973-1979 (Box 46:, Folder 1557)
  - Kennelly, James, 1969-1974 (Box 46:, Folder 1558)
  - Killian, Robert, 1972-1974 (Box 46:, Folder 1559)
  - Killingly letters, 1975-1977 (Box 46:, Folder 1560)
  - Legislation, 1977 (Box 46:, Folder 1561)
  - Library—Faith Hektoem, 1975-1976 (Box 46:, Folder 1562)
  - Lieberman, J., 1974 (Box 46:, Folder 1563)
  - Mansfield letters, 1969-1975 (Box 46:, Folder 1564)
  - Mansfield letters, 1976-1978 (Box 46:, Folder 1565)
  - Out of district letters, 1969-1976 (Box 46:, Folder 1566)
  - Out of district letters, 1969-1974 (Box 46:, Folder 1567)
  - Out of district letters, 1977-1979 (Box 46:, Folder 1568)
  - Plainfield letters, 1975-1977 (Box 46:, Folder 1569)
  - Political, 1955-1974 (Box 46:, Folder 1570)
  - Political, 1975 (Box 46:, Folder 1571)
  - Political, 1976-1979 (Box 46:, Folder 1572)
  - Political, 1977-1983 (Box 47:, Folder 1573)
  - Political, 1980 (Box 47:, Folder 1574)
  - Political, 1981-1982 (Box 47:, Folder 1575)
  - Political, 1983 (Box 47:, Folder 1576)
  - Prayer in schools, 1975 (Box 47:, Folder 1577)
  - Putnam letters, 1975-1977 (Box 47:, Folder 1578)
  - Ratchford, William, 1969-1974 (Box 47:, Folder 1579)
  - Recommendations, undated (Box 47:, Folder 1580)
  - Ribicoff, A., 1968-1976 (Box 47:, Folder 1581)
  - Seminars, 1972-1982 (Box 47:, Folder 1582)
  - Tax opposition—constituents, 1975-1977 (Box 47:, Folder 1583)
  - Thank you letters, 1972-1976 (Box 47:, Folder 1584)
  - Thompson letters, 1975-1977 (Box 47:, Folder 1585)
  - Willimantic letters, 1969-1975 (Box 47:, Folder 1586)
  - Willimantic letters, 1976 (Box 47:, Folder 1587)
- Series XI: Publications, 1959-1983
  - Advisory Commission on Intergovernmental Relations, 1976-1978 (Box 47:, Folder 1588)
  - Advisory Commission on Intergovernmental Relations, 1979-1980 (Box 47:, Folder 1589)
  - Advisory Commission on Intergovernmental Relations, 1981 (Box 47:, Folder 1590)
  - Agriculture, 1980 (Box 47:, Folder 1591)
  - Citizen's Committee for Effective Government, Inc., 1980-1981 (Box 47:, Folder 1592)
  - Connecticut and Hartford economy, 1959-1979 (Box 47:, Folder 1593)
  - Connecticut and Hartford economy, 1978-1980 (Box 47:, Folder 1594)
  - Connecticut and Hartford economy, 1980-1981 (Box 47:, Folder 1595)
  - Connecticut and Hartford economy, 1981 (Box 47:, Folder 1596)
  - Connecticut and Hartford economy, 1981 (Box 48:, Folder 1597)
  - Connecticut and Hartford economy, 1982 (Box 48:, Folder 1598)
  - Connecticut Business and Industry Association, 1980 (Box 48:, Folder 1599)
  - Connecticut Conference of Municipalities, 1979-1983 (Box 48:, Folder 1600)
  - Connecticut Humanities Council, 1980 (Box 48:, Folder 1601)
  - Connecticut State Employees, 1979-1981 (Box 48:, Folder 1602)
  - Connecticut Real Estate and Urban Economic Studies (CREUES), 1978-1979 (Box 48:, Folder 1603)
  - Energy and environment, 1976-1979 (Box 48:, Folder 1604)
  - Energy and environment, 1977-1981 (Box 48:, Folder 1605)
  - Ex-POW bulletin, 1977-1980 (Box 48:, Folder 1606)
  - Federal budgeting, 1981-1982 (Box 48:, Folder 1607)
  - Federation of Public Programs in the Humanities, 1979-1980 (Box 48:, Folder 1608)
  - Government Printing Office (GPO), 1973 (Box 48:, Folder 1609)
  - Health, 1979-1980 (Box 48:, Folder 1610)
  - Health: Drugs, 1977-1978 (Box 48:, Folder 1611)
  - Institute of Urban Research, 1979 (Box 48:, Folder 1612-1613)
  - Judicial Compensation, 1979 (Box 48:, Folder 1614)
  - Laurel Club Bulletin, 1969 (Box 48:, Folder 1615)
  - Legislative Program Review and Investigation Committee, 1982 (Box 48:, Folder 1616)
  - National Conference of State Legislatures, 1979-1981 (Box 48:, Folder 1617)
  - National Governor's Association, 1981 (Box 48:, Folder 1618-1619)
  - Planning and preservation, 1974 (Box 49:, Folder 1620)
  - Planning and preservation, 1975-1980 (Box 49:, Folder 1621)
  - Planning and preservation, 1981-1982 (Box 49:, Folder 1622)
  - Regional Associations and Studies, 1976-1981 (Box 49:, Folder 1623)
  - State Government, Council of, 1978-1982 (Box 49:, Folder 1624)
  - State Government, Council of, 1976-1981 (Box 49:, Folder 1625)
  - State Governments, Council of, 1978-1979 (Box 49:, Folder 1626)
  - U.S. Department of Commerce, 1971-1975 (Box 49:, Folder 1627)
  - U.S. Railway Association, v. I, 1975 (Box 49:, Folder 1628)
  - U.S. Railway Association, v. II, 1975 (Box 49:, Folder 1629)
  - Willimantic Annual Report, 1981-1982 (Box 49:, Folder 1630)
- Series XII: Personal Materials, 1954-1983
  - Bills, 1979-1981 (Box 49:, Folder 1631)
  - Certification and Vitae, 1971-1976 (Box 49:, Folder 1632)
  - Connecticut General Employment, 1980-1981 (Box 49:, Folder 1633)
  - Employment Records, 1954-1978 (Box 49:, Folder 1634)
  - Income Tax, 1980-1981 (Box 49:, Folder 1635)
  - Personal letters and notes, undated (Box 49:, Folder 1636-1637)
  - Personal letters and notes, 1979-1980 (Box 49:, Folder 1638)
  - Personal letters and notes, 1981 (Box 49:, Folder 1639)
  - Personal letters and notes, 1982-1983 (Box 49:, Folder 1640)
  - Personal pocket planners, 1982-1983 (Box 50:, Folder 1641)
  - Resume, 1982 (Box 50:, Folder 1642)
  - Sleigh blanket, 1982 (Box 50:, Folder 1643)
- Series XIII: Photographs, undated
  - Photographs
- Series XIV: Memorabilia, undated
  - Ribbons, badges, etc. (Box 51)
  - Dixon, Ralph: Beck Lawyer, 1980 (Box RESTRICTED:)